Koopman family papers
Connecticut Historical Society
- I. Moses Fox (1850-1938)
  - National Retail Dry Goods Association Board of Directors Resolution on the death of Moses Fox, April 12, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    (see OVERSIZE #1 in Box 12)
  - Southern New England Ice Co. Coupon Book, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1930, 1935, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Death Notices, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings from marked "Hartford Dun Reports,", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Congregation Beth Israel (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dr. Pendleton’s Sanatorium postcard & directions, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- II. Beatrice Fox Auerbach (1887-1968)
  - A. Correspondence
    - General correspondence, 1906-1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Auerbach, Fannie Fox, correspondence, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence from George S. Auerbach, June-August 1910 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence from George S. Auerbach, September 1910 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence from George S. Auerbach, October 1910 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence from George S. Auerbach, December 1-15, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence from George S. Auerbach, December 16-31, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence from George S. Auerbach, January 1-20, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence from George S. Auerbach, January 21-31, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence from George S. Auerbach, February 1911 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Chemical Bank & Trust Company, correspondence, 1937-1942 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, correspondence, 1946-1962, [photocopies of originals] (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence from Beatrice Fox Auerbach to her family while abroad, 1957-1959, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - B. Diaries and Journals
    - "My Trip Abroad in 1900" (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Journal, Summer of 1904 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Journal, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "Automobile Trip, Fox-Plaut May 1908" (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Log Book, of West Indies Cruise, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Year Books, 1942, 1943, [mostly empty] (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Travel Journal [1949] (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "A Diary of My Summer Holiday with Chase Woodhouse as a delightful companion when we visited Greece, Turkey, Lebanon, Syria, Iran, Trans-Jordan, Israel, Old Jerusalem, Switzerland, and Germany, August 18, 1949-October 9,1949", [copy 1] (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "A Diary of My Summer Holiday with Chase Woodhouse as a delightful companion when we visited Greece, Turkey, Lebanon, Syria, Iran, Trans-Jordan, Israel, Old Jerusalem, Switzerland, and Germany, August 18, 1949-October 9,1949", [copy 2] (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Near East Trip, August 1950- October 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "A Diary: My Trip with Chase Woodhouse Through the Lands of the Far East, 1951" (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - "Letters to my Family: A Three Months’ Journey Through the Great Continent of Africa, South of the Sahara, with Chase Woodhouse as a Traveling Companion, April 30-July 30, 1953" (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - C. Foundations and Associations
    - Beatrice Fox Auerbach Foundation – Memorial Submitted on behalf of the Muslim Educational Association of Southern India, Madras, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Beatrice Fox Auerbach Foundation – Meeting Materials, 1951, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Beatrice Fox Auerbach Foundation – Scholarship Committee, 1951, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Connecticut 4H Auerbach Farm, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Council of Jewish Women – Social Welfare Report, May 14, 1924. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Governor’s Foot Guard Dog Show, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Governor’s Foot Guard Dog Show, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Governor’s Foot Guard Dog Show, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Governor’s Foot Guard Dog Show, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Governor’s Foot Guard Dog Show, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Hartford Foundation for Public Giving – "Generations,", [ca. 1995] (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Hartford Woman’s Club – Year Books, 1926-1927, 1927-1928, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Ladies Literary Club of Cortland [New York?] – "A Woman of Business, Not a Business Woman," (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Ladies Visiting Committee – Annual Report, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Service Bureau for Women’s Organizations – Annual Report, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Service Bureau for Women’s Organizations – Annual Report, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Service Bureau for Women’s Organizations – Annual Report, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Service Bureau for Women’s Organizations – Annual Report, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Service Bureau for Women’s Organizations – Brochures, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Service Bureau for Women’s Organizations – Meeting, January 19, [1946] (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Service Bureau for Women’s Organizations – The Eleanor Roosevelt Story with inscription to Beatrice Fox Auerbach, Christmas 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Social Welfare, n.d. [ca. 1917-1925] (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Tobé Bosses Dinner, 1938-1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Tobé-Coburn School for Fashion Careers – Graduation Exercises, June 5, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum – Annual Report, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - D. Awards and Honors
    - Certificate of Participation in contributing to the cost of the Fighter Plane "City of Hartford,", November 1942 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Testimonial of Appreciation to Mrs. B.F. Auerbach from Frederick Atkins, Inc. Controllers’ Group, April 1945; see OVERSIZE #2 in Box 12 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Tobé Award, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - A Tribute to Beatrice Fox Auerbach, Tobé Award Winner for 1947, January 14, 1948; see OVERSIZE #3 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Wesleyan University Honorary Degree, June 19, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Certificates given by: Trinity College, June 1951 and New York University, May 1951; see OVERSIZE # 4 in Box 12 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Trinity College, 125th Commencement Program, June 17, 1951 [3 copies] and Trinity College Bulletin, Alumni News Issue, July 1951 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Hillyer College Honorary Degree, June 12, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Certificate of Life Membership in the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, December 1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - American Legion Auxiliary Most Distinguished Service Citation, [1959] (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - The 1962 Distinguished Public Service Award of the State Bar Association of Connecticut, October 16, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Connecticut-Western Massachusetts Region of the National Conference of Christians and Jews – National Human Relations Award, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Junior Achievement Free Enterprise Hall of Fame Awards Banquet, February 25, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Dedication of Beatrice Fox Auerbach Computer & Administration Center, April 20, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 22a)
    - My Sisters’ Place: A Celebration of Hartford Heroines,April 5, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22b)
    - Connecticut Women’s Hall of Fame Inaugural Event, May 19, 1994 [2 copies] (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - The National Cyclopedia for American Biography, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - E. Financial
    - Annual Account of the Estate of Moses Fox, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Auerfarm Cash Notebook, 1925-1926 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Auerfarm Ledger, 1925-1936 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], January 1924 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], February 1924 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], March 1924 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], April 1924 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], May 1924 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], June 1924 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], July 1924 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], December 1924 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], January 1925; Note: When processing the collection, there was no bank statement for February 1925. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], March 1925 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], April 1925 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], May 1925 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], June 1925 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], July 1925 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], August 1925 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], September 1925 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], October 1925 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], November 1925 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], December 1925 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1922-1923 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bills & Receipts, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Check Register, April 1917-March 1918 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Check Register, July-December 1919 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Check Register, September 1925-May 1927 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Estimates for work on 1040 Prospect Ave, 1929-1936 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Family Expense Record, 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Family Expense Record, January 1932 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - G. Fox &Co. Bills, 1924, 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Income Statements, 1923-1924, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Phoenix State Bank &Trust Company – blank checks, [ca. 1920s] (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Phoenix State Bank &Trust Company – Deposit Book, 1926-1928 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Riverside Trust Company – checkbook [blank] (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Stock Dividends, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Walker Brothers Bankers, 1919-1920 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - F. Academic Records
    - Beacon School – Writing Notebook, November 8, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Beacon School – Literature Notebook, 1361 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Benjamin Deane School – History Notebook, 1905-1906 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Huntsinger Business School, Inc. – 20th Century Bookkeeping and Accounting Complete, 1917; [with handwritten notes] (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - G. Scrapbooks and Guest Books
    - Scrapbook of theater programs, 1899-1909 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings about George S. Auerbach’s death, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Scrapbook Memorial to George S. Auerbach, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Scrapbook Memorial to George S. Auerbach, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook Memorial to George S. Auerbach, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook Memorial to George S. Auerbach, 1927; Note: The memorial scrapbooks from Box 4, Folder 27 and Box 5, Folders 1, 2, and 3 have some small differences, but mostly contain the same information (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings about the deaths of Moses Fox, Isaac Fox, Jacob Fox, Morris F. Marks, and Fred S. Auerbach, see OVERSIZE #5 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings about Moses Fox’s birthdays, his gifts to the City of Hartford, and the deaths of Moses Fox, Isaac Fox, Jacob Fox, Morris F. Marks, and Fred S. Auerbach, see OVERSIZE #6 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, September 1931-April 1948; see OVERSIZE #7 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook of Christmas cards sent by Beatrice Fox Auerbach, 1929-1966; see OVERSIZE #8; card for 1952-1953 in Box 12 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook of monthly cards sent by Beatrice Fox Auerbach, 1948-1965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Guest Book, 1914-1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Guest Log, 1940-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Guest Book, June 1943-August 1966; see OVERSIZE #9 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Guest Book, October 1957-September 1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - H. Newspaper Clippings
    - Auerfarm, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Beatrice Fox Auerbach Foundation, 1982, 1997, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Appearances, 1965, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Awards &Honors, 1948-2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Congressional Record – Extensions of Remarks, January 8, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Connecticut Magazine – "God Bless You, Mrs. Auerbach,", March 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Death Notices, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Foundations & Associations, 1959, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - The Hartford Courant – Our Century: A Commemorative Edition, Sunday, December 5, 1999, Section D: Business [see page D5], see OVERSIZE #10 in Box 12 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - House on 1040 Prospect Avenue, 1990, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - "Mementos of Mrs. Beatrice Auerbach (from January 1943 to February 1964)" to Mrs. Fan Samuels from Estelle Hamburger, June 4, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Northeast Magazine, May 4, 1986 "Beatrice Fox Auerbach" [2 copies], see OVERSIZE #11 in Box 12 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Sponsorship of citizenship, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Travels Abroad, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Tributes, 1965-1999, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - University of Hartford, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - I. Assorted Papers
    - Legal – Historical Survey of Real Estate Transactions Engaged in by Gerson Fox and his son Moses Fox, prepared, April 1938 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Legal – Power of Attorney, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - The American Society of Certified Public Accountants memorandum, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Inventory of Household Belongings, n.d., for handwritten copy see OVERSIZE #12 in Box 12 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Contents of Trunk for Mrs. Auerbach’s House, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - The Bride’s Book, 1910-1911 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Honeymoon Gazette, 1911; see OVERSIZE #37 in Box 12 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Wedding List, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Travel Itineraries, 1910, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Birthday Listing of Remembrances, 1976; Auerfarm Menu; Poems, 1957; Program for Testimonial Dinner to Frederick Atkins, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Ephemera (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - "Toasts" (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Memorial from the Board of Directors of the May Co., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - American Kennel Club Registration Certificate, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - American Red Cross Course Completion Certificate, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Directions for Loading Camera (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Notes regarding her mother’s will and religious education (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Calendars, 1923, 1926 &1927 with notes on reverse (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Small Notebooks, n.d. [mostly empty] (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Biographical Information (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "Beatrice Fox Auerbach – Connecticut Women of the Century," Channel 3, WFSB-TV, Nov 18, 1999 (Videocassette, 0:65), in Box 11: Audio-Visual Materials, 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - "Beatrice Fox Auerbach," WFSB-TV, Nov 18, 1999 (Videocassette, 1:00), in Box 11: Audio-Visual Materials, 2 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- III. George S. Auerbach (1885-1927)
  - Correspondence to Moses and Theresa Stern Fox, 1910-1911 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Legal – Estate & Inventory, 1927-1928 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Legal – Standard Investment Co., 1923, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Financial – Bank Statements [with cancelled checks], January - July 1921 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Financial – Bank Statements [with cancelled checks], August - December 1921 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Financial – Bank Statements [with cancelled checks], January - May 1924 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Financial – Bank Statements [with cancelled checks], June - October 1924 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Financial – Bank Statements [with cancelled checks], November - December 1924 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Financial – Bank Statements [with cancelled checks], January - April 1925 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Financial – Bank Statements [with cancelled checks], May - July 1925; Note: When processing the collection, there was no bank statement for August 1925. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Financial – Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], September 1925 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Financial – Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], November 1925 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Financial – Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], December 1925 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Financial – Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], March 1926 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Financial – Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], April 1926 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Financial – Bank Statement [with cancelled checks], May 1926 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Financial – Bills & Receipts, A – C (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Financial – Bills & Receipts, D – L (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Financial – Bills & Receipts, M – W (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Financial – G. Fox & Co. Bills to his Estate, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Financial – Income Tax Statements, 1925-1926 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Financial – Walker Brothers Bankers, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Financial – Walker Brothers Bankers, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Foundations & Associations – The Rotary Club of Hartford, 1926, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Foundations & Associations – The Rotary Club of Hartford, Yearbook, 1927-1928; [copy 1] (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Foundations & Associations – The Rotary Club of Hartford, Yearbook, 1927-1928; [copy 2] (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Foundations & Associations – Tumble Brook Country Club, Inc. – Resolution of Appreciation, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Ephemera, 1919, 1927-28, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Notebooks & Wallet, [mostly empty] (Box 6, Folder 44)
- IV. Koopman Family
  - A. Georgette Auerbach Koopman
    - Correspondence, 1932-2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Awards & Honors, 1968-2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Events – Avon Old Farms Horse Show, October 18, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Events – "A Star is Reborn,", December 7, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Financial – Auerbach Realty Company Financial Statements, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Financial – Family Service Society, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Financial – Foreign Imports, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Financial – G. Fox & Co. Bills, 1932-1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Financial – G. Fox & Co. Expenses, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Financial – The Koopman Fund, Inc. Auditors’ Report, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Financial – Wedding Expenses, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Foundations & Associations – Department of Environmental Protection, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Foundations & Associations – Goodspeed Opera House, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Foundations & Associations – The Greater Hartford Jewish Federation, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Foundations & Associations – Hartford Art School – History, 1977-2002, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Foundations & Associations – Hartford Art School – Publications, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Foundations & Associations – Hartford Art School – Trustees, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Foundations & Associations – Hartford Art School – Assorted Materials, 1997, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Foundations & Associations – Hartford Artisans’ Center, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Foundations & Associations – League of Women Voters, 1972-1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Foundations & Associations – The Noah Webster Foundation and Historical Society of West Hartford, Inc., 1986, 1991, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Foundations & Associations – Parent-Teacher Organization, 1951-1964, n.d (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau for Connecticut Organizations [Service Bureau] – Annual Report, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau – Annual Report, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau – Annual Report, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau – Annual Report, 1973 [copy 1] (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau – Annual Report, 1973 [copy 2] (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau – Annual Report, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau – Publications – The Legal Rights of Children, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau – Publications – School Law, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Foundations & Associations – Service Bureau – Assorted Papers, 1980, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Foundations & Associations – University of Hartford, 2001, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Foundations & Associations – Wartime Civil Defense, 1941-1942 [1 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Foundations & Associations – Wartime Civil Defense, 1941-1942 [2 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Academic Records – Noah Webster School, Notebook, 1924-1925 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Academic Records – Oxford Chat, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Academic Records – Oxford Chat, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Academic Records – Oxford School, Grade 2 Composition Book, ca. 1928 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Academic Records – Oxford School, Exercises & Tests in Algebra, ca. 1929 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Academic Records – Notebook of American History, 1932-1933 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Academic Records – Science Scrap Book, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Academic Records – Oxford Alumnae Bulletin, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Service Program, April 9, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Ephemera, 1943, 1976, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings – Awards & Honors, 1972, 1988, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings – The Endowment Fund of the Greater Hartford Jewish Federation, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings – Engagement & Wedding Announcements, 1940, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper Clippings – Foundations & Associations, 1964-1999, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper Clippings – Governor’s Horse Guard Show, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper Clippings – Society News, 1935, 1991, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings – University of Hartford, 1979-1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - B. Richard Koopman
    - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Financial, 1943-1952 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Awards & Honors – Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce, May 25, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Foundations & Associations – Aetna, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Foundations & Associations – The Hartford Club, 1974-75, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Foundations & Associations – Hartford Foundation for Public Giving, 1966, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Foundations & Associations – Hartford National Corporation, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Foundations & Associations – The Southern New England Telephone Company, 1972, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Foundations & Associations – St. John’s Lodge No. 4 of Free and Accepted Masons, April 28, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Foundations & Associations – Vassar Club of Hartford, 1972-73, 1980-81 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Army Handbook, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - May Department Stores Company, Annual Report, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1968, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Newspaper Clippings – Mount Sinai Hospital, 1957-1966 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Newspaper Clippings – Obituaries, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- V. Other Family Members and Associates
  - Auerbach, Frederick F. (1927-1998) – Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Auerbach, Frederick S. (1890-1938) – Newspaper Clippings, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Fox, Gerson (1811-1880) – Account Book, 1829-1858 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Fox, Gerson (1811-1880) – Probate, Estate, & Inventory, 1880-1881 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Fox, Gerson (1811-1880) – Warrantee Deed, September 25, 1879 (Box 8, Folder 31)